<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="Recipe">
        <item>
            1 cup milk
            ¾ cup sugar
            2 tablespoons unsweetened cocoa powder
            ¼ teaspoon salt
            3 egg yolk, lightly beaten
            2 ounces semisweet chocolate, chopped
            2 cups heavy cream
            1 teaspoon vanilla extract
            Steps:
            Combine milk, sugar, cocoa powder, and salt in a saucepan over medium heat. Bring to a simmer, stirring constantly.
            Place egg yolks into a small bowl. Gradually whisk in about 1/2 cup of hot milk mixture, then return to the saucepan. Heat and stir until thickened, but do not boil.
            Remove from the heat and stir in chopped chocolate until melted.
            Pour into a chilled bowl and refrigerate, stirring occasionally, until cold, about 2 hours.
            Stir in cream and vanilla. Pour into an ice cream maker and freeze according to manufacturer's directions.
        </item>
        <item>
            1 tablespoon vegetable oil
            ½ onion, chopped
            2 teaspoons minced garlic
            1 (10.5 ounce) can condensed cream of mushroom soup
            ½ cup milk
            1 tablespoon Worcestershire sauce
            15 frozen beef meatballs, or more to taste
            8 ounces broad egg white noodles (such as No Yolks®)
            ¾ cup sour cream
            salt and ground black pepper to taste
            Steps:
            Heat oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat. Add onion and garlic; cook and stir until onion is almost soft, about 3 minutes.
            Reduce heat to medium; stir in condensed soup, milk, and Worcestershire sauce. Add meatballs; reduce heat to low and simmer, covered, until tender, 35 to 40 minutes.
            Meanwhile, bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add noodles and cook, stirring occasionally, until tender yet firm to the bite, 10 to 12 minutes; drain.
            Add sour cream, salt, and pepper to meatballs in sauce. Cook until flavors combine, about 2 minutes. Serve meatballs over noodles.
        </item>
        <item>
            1 (16 ounce) package uncooked rotini pasta
            1 (16 ounce) bottle Italian salad dressing
            2 cucumbers, chopped
            6 tomatoes, chopped
            1 bunch green onions, chopped
            4 ounces grated Parmesan cheese
            1 tablespoon Italian seasoning
            Steps:
            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Place pasta in the pot, cook for 8 to 12 minutes, until al dente, and drain.
            Toss cooked pasta with Italian dressing, cucumbers, tomatoes, and green onions in a large bowl. Mix Parmesan cheese and Italian seasoning in a small bowl, and gently mix into the salad.
            Cover, and refrigerate for at least 30 minutes before serving.
        </item>
        <item>
            1 lb chicken breast, cut into chunks
            1 teaspoon garlic powder
            1/2 teaspoon salt
            1/2 teaspoon pepper
            1 tablespoon olive oil
            3 cloves garlic, minced
            3/4 cup long grain white rice
            2 1/2 cups Progresso™ chicken broth
            2 cups baby spinach
            2 tablespoons heavy cream
            Steps:
            Toss the chicken breast with garlic powder, salt, and pepper. Heat olive oil in a 10-inch skillet over medium heat. Add chicken breast and cook until browned, stirring often, about 3 minutes. Add garlic to skillet and cook for 30 seconds more.
            Stir in rice and chicken broth. Bring to a boil, reduce to a simmer, and cover. Cook for 20 minutes, stirring occasionally.
            Remove pan from heat and place baby spinach on top of the rice. Cover and let sit for 5 minutes.
            Remove lid and stir well. Stir in cream and serve.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>